Guide to the Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 4
Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 4
- Box: 76, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - Item 63: Press Release - An ETUC delegation, 1979; Publication (Box 76, Folder 15)
    Notes: Information - CP32/79
  - Item 64: European Trade Unionists meet Mr. Cheysson, 1979; Publication (Box 76, Folder 15)
    Notes: Information - CP36/79
  - Item 65: Social Security, 1979; Publication (Box 76, Folder 15)
    Notes: Information - 37/79
  - Item 66: ETUC President in Strasbourg, 1979; Publication (Box 76, Folder 15)
    Notes: Information - 38/79
  - Item 67: Press Release -- ETUC appeal to the workers of Europe, 1978; Publication (Box 76, Folder 15)
    Notes: Information - CP/4/78
  - Item 68: Press Release -- The Executive Committee of the European Trade Union, 1978; Publication (Box 76, Folder 15)
    Notes: Information -- CPGG/6/78
  - Item 69: Information obligations of multinational groups of companies, Publication (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - Item 70: ETUC Statement to Bremen European Council, 1978; Publication (Box 76, Folder 15)
    Notes: Information
  - Item 71: Press Release -- The ETUC and the Bremen European Council, 1978; Publication (Box 76, Folder 15)
    Notes: Information - CPSG 7/78
  - Item 72: Meeting of the Committee on the Control of the Application of the Social Charter, 1978; Publication (Box 76, Folder 15)
    Notes: Informaiton - CPGS 10/78
  - Item 73: Press Release - The Executive Committee of the European Trade Union Confederation, 1978; Publication (Box 76, Folder 15)
    Notes: Information - CPGS 11/78
  - Item 74: Advisory Committee on distribution and trade, 1978; Publication (Box 76, Folder 15)
    Notes: Information - 14/78
- Box: 77, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Report of credentials committee, 1990; Publication (Box 77, Folder 1)
    Author: Organisation of African Trade Union Unity
  - Item 2: Organisation of African Trade Union Unity, 1987; Publication (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Voice of African Workers, 1986; Publication (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Voice of African Workers, 1986; Publication (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Organization of African Trade Union Unity -- To: All Fraternal Trade Union Organizations, 1986; Publication (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Organisation of African Trade Union Unity -- Joint Communique between the visiting un special committee against Apartheid with the Secretariat of the Organisation of African Trade Unio nUnity to Accra, 1977; Publication (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Organisation de L'Unite Syndicale Africaine - Resolutions adoptees par le troisieme Congres Ordinaire Tenu a Mogadiscio, 1980; Publication (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Qu'est - Ce que l'Ousa?, 1978; Publication (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Qu'est - Ce que l'Ousa?, 1978; Publication (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: What is OATUU?, Publication (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: What is OATUU?, Publication (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Organisation of African Trade Union Unity (OATUU), Publication (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: Organisation of African Trade Union Unity (OATUU), Publication (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: Organisation of African Trade Union Unity (OATUU), Publication (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Item 15: Organisation of African Trade Union Unity (OATUU), Publication (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: Second Congress of the OATUU, Tripoli, Libya, 20-23, April, 1976: preamble, Publication (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: Resolutions of the 4th General Council Meeting (April 11th-14th, 1979), Arusha (Tanzania), Publication (Box 77, Folder 1)
- Box: 77, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: EC-US Fishing agreement nets EC Council approval, 1984; Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
    Author: European community Information Service
    Notes: European Community News
  - Item 2: EC supports deployment of multinational forces in Beirut, 1982; Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: US-EC Steel Accord should diffuse trade tensions, 1982; Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: 25th Anniversary of the European Community, 1982; Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: US relations with the European Community, 1981; Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: European Parliament resolution on Israeli raid, 1981; Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: The European Automobile Industry: structure and prospects, 1981; Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Meeting of the European Council in Luxembourg, 1981; Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: President Thorn to visit Washington, 1981; Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Meeting between President Thorn and Prime Minister Trudeau, 1981; Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: This Month in the European Parliament, 1981; Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: Sunburst design wins competition for European Community Pavilions, 1981; Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: Statement by President Gaston Thorn, 1981; Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Item 14: Excerpts of speech by H.E. Roland de Kergorlay, 1981; Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Item 15: European inventory of Chemical Substances, 1981; Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Item 16: The Community's Emergency Aid to Developing Countries, 1981; Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Item 17: Statement by President Jenkins at his farewell Press Conference, 1981; Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Item 18: First meeting of the new commission of the European Communities, 1981; Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Item 19: Greece joins the European Community, 1981; Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Item 20: 1982 Energy Expo: European Community Pavilion Contract, 1981; Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Item 21: Agricultural aid to Poland, 1981; Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Item 22: Secretary of State Alexander Haig visits, 1981; Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Item 23: European Parliamentary delegation to visit Washington, 1981; Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Item 24: Generalized system of preferences 1981, Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Item 25: Second Anniversary of the EMS, 1981; Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Item 26: Conclusions of the European Council, 1980; Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Item 27: Agriculture and Foreign Policy, 1982; Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Item 28: Trade relations between industrialized countries in times of crisis, 1982; Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Item 29: President Jenkins' statement to the European Parliament on the outcome of the European Council in Venice, 1980; Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Item 30: European Community - United States Relations: Twisting the Dragon's tail, 1982; Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Item 31: EC Publishes comparative data for 22 nations, 1984; Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Item 32: Most Eurpeans support Environmental Protection abour Economic growth, 1984; Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Item 33: Greenland and the EC will maintain close ties after Greenland's withdrawal, 1984; Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Item 34: EC acts to facilitate wine trade with the US, 1984; Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Item 35: EC surveys show support for a United Europe, 1984; Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Item 36: EC approves IBM personal computer distribution; investigation continues on IBM mainframe computer practices, 1984; Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Item 37: The New Orleans "World Fair to celebrate European Day, 1984; Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Item 38: European Parliament Elections to take place June 14-17, Fact Sheet, 1984; Publication (Box 77, Folder 2)
- Box: 77, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: EFTA bulletin, 1981; Publication (Box 77, Folder 3)
    Author: European Free Trade Association
    Notes: v.22:no.2
  - Item 2: EFTA bulletin, 1977; Publication (Box 77, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.28
- Box: 77, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Satzung, 2006; Publication (Box 77, Folder 4)
    Author: Germany Trade Union Federation
- Box: 77, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Price control and the maintenance of purchasing power in Western Europe, 1981; Publication (Box 77, Folder 5)
    Author: European Trade Union Institute
    Notes: Press Release
  - Item 2: New report on privatisation in Western Europe, 1988; Publication (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Pensioners in Western Europe, 1988; Publication (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: The European Trade Union Confederation: its history, structure and policies, 1990; Publication (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: The trade union movement in Belgium, 1987; Publication (Box 77, Folder 5)
    Author: Martin Hutsebaut
  - Item 6: The trade union movement in Austria: the OGB, 1985; Publication (Box 77, Folder 5)
    Author: Guner Kopke
- Box: 77, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Trade union action against the pharmaceutical transnational companies, 1981; Publication (Box 77, Folder 6)
- Box: 77, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Action of metalworkers' unions for peace and social progress, 1987; Publication (Box 77, Folder 7)
    Author: International Conference of Metalworkers Trade Unions
  - Item 2: Action of metalworkers' unions for peace and social progress, 1987; Publication (Box 77, Folder 7)
- Box: 77, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: ILO Director-General tells conference: assured financing, 1988; Publication (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: ILO conference concludes "Human Rights", 1988; Publication (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: ILO conference adopts new conventions and report on appleication of standards, 1978; Publication (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: ILO issues social and labour study on six, 1977; Publication (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Theme of new book: International Labour standards in the cause of human rights, 1978; Publication (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: Standards on labour administration to be discussed by ILO Conference, 1978; Publication (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: Standards on labour administration to be discussed by ILO Conference, 1978; Publication (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Item 8: Theme of new book: International Labour standards in the cause of human rights, 1978; Publication (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Item 9: Fewer strikes in IMEC countries but more days lost in europe, 1979; Publication (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Item 10: Fewer strikes in IMEC countries but more days lost in europe, 1979; Publication (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Item 11: Fewer strikes in IMEC countries but more days lost in europe, 1979; Publication (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Item 12: ILO's 60th Anniv. Conference, 1979; Publication (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Item 13: ILO's 60th Anniv. Conference, 1979; Publication (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Item 14: ILO's 60th Anniv. Conference, 1979; Publication (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Item 15: ILO's 60th Anniv. Conference, 1979; Publication (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Item 16: ILO charts progress achieved through standards, 1976; Publication (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Item 17: ILO governing body plus multinationals, employment, dock work and road transport on priority list, 1976; Publication (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Item 18: ILO drive to improve working environment, reduce accidents at work, 1976; Publication (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Item 19: Plantation workers earning less than $1 a day, ILO Committee told, 1976; Publication (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Item 20: Work begins on declaration of principles for multinationals, 1977; Publication (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Item 21: New phase in campaign to protect workers, 1977; Publication (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Item 22: Increasing role of labour administration will get special study at ILO conference, 1977; Publication (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Item 23: ILO draft declaration on multinational enterprises, 1977; Publication (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Item 24: Rights of public servants to be discussed by International Labour Conference, 1977; Publication (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Item 25: Rights of public servants to be discussed by International Labour Conference, 1977; Publication (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Item 26: Spain ratifies two ILO conventions on freedom of association, 1977; Publication (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Item 27: Spain ratifies two ILO conventions on freedom of association, 1977; Publication (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Item 28: Use of computer in industrial relations is subject of experts meeting at ILO, 1977; Publication (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Item 29: 45 countries improved labour laws, says ILO, 1977; Publication (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Item 30: International Labour Conference Act on Health protection at work, 1977; Publication (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Item 31: Training of workers' representatives for participation in decisions within undertakings to be discussed at ILO symposium, 1977; Publication (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Item 32: ILO issues social and labour study on six, 1977; Publication (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Item 33: Vienna meeting on collective bargaining in industrial countries, 1977; Publication (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Item 34: World's management development institutions create permanent contact system at ILO, 1980; Publication (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Item 35: ILO conference to examine stronger safeguards for workers facing dismissal, 1981; Publication (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Item 36: ILO conference to examine stronger safeguards for workers facing dismissal, 1981; Publication (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Item 37: ILO conference to examine stronger safeguards for workers facing dismissal, 1981; Publication (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Item 38: Forward-looking measues on social security and technological training urged by the ILO European conference, 1987; Publication (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Item 39: ILO head stresses faster European growth and solidarity with underprivileged nations, 1987; Publication (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Item 40: ILO governing body: New standards envisaged on night work and on the use of chemicals, 1987; Publication (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Item 41: Europes managers and trainers face up to technological change, 1987; Publication (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Item 42: Two-fold solution needed for occupied Arab territories, says ILO Director-General, 1988; Publication (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Item 43: ILO governing body notes cases of progress in freedom of associaiton cases, 1988; Publication (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Item 44: Fundamental shifts in working time to be examined by ILO meeting, 1988; Publication (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Item 45: Workers, Housewives, MothersAfrican women need help to progress on many fronts, 1988; Publication (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Item 46: ILO meeting spotlights public service labour relations, 1988; Publication (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Item 47: ILO meeting seeks improved public service labour relations and social security, 1988; Publication (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Item 48: New international standards planned by ILO to protect workers in insolvency cases, 1991; Publication (Box 77, Folder 8)
- Box: 77, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Statutes of the IFBWW = Statuts de la FITBB = IBBH Satzung = IBTU:s stadgar = Estatutos de la FITCM, 1994; Publication (Box 77, Folder 9)
    Author: International Federation of Building and Wood Workers
    Language: English; French; German; Swedish; Spanish.
  - Item 2: Statutes of the IFBWW = Statuts de la FITBB = IBBH Satzung = IBTU:s stadgar = Estatutos de la FITCM, 1994; Publication (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Statutes = Statuts = Satzung = Stadgar = Estatutos, 1978; Publication (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Statutes = Statuts = Satzung = Stadgar = Estatutos, 1978; Publication (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Statutes = Statuts = Satzung = Stadgar = Estatutos, 1978; Publication (Box 77, Folder 9)
- Box: 77, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: International Federation of Building and Wood Workers: IFBWW, Publication (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: IFBWW Executive Committee Elected at the 19th World Congress, Publication (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Resolutions adopted by the IFBWW 19th Congress 4-8 October 1993, the Hague, Netherlands, Publication (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: IFBWW 19th World Congress 4-8 October 1993, the Hague, Netherlands, Publication (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: IFBWW Executive Committee Elected at the 19th World Congress, 1993; Publication (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: Subject: Decisions of the IFBWW 19th World Congress 4-8 October 1993, the Hague, Netherlands, Publication (Box 77, Folder 10)
    Notes: circular
  - Item 7: Circular, Circulaire, Cirkular, Rundschreiben No. 47, 1995; Publication (Box 77, Folder 10)
    Language: English; French; Swedish; German.
  - Item 8: Circular, Circulaire, Cirkular, Rundschreiben No. 9, 1998; Publication (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Item 9: Forest action programme, 1992; Publication (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Item 10: Forest action programme, 1992; Publication (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Item 11: The International Federation o fBuilding and Wood Workers, Publication (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Item 12: FaxNews - no. 1 (1991), Publication (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Item 13: IFBWW programme of action: 1990-1993, Publication (Box 77, Folder 10)
- Box: 77, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Resolutions adopted by the IFBWW 19th Congress 4-8 October 1993, the Hague, Netherlands, Publication (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Resolutions adopted by the IFBWW 19th Congress 4-8 October 1993, the Hague, Netherlands, Publication (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Resolutions adopted by the IFBWW 19th Congress 4-8 October 1993, the Hague, Netherlands, Publication (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: IFBWW Executive Committee Elected at the 19th World Congress, Publication (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: IFBWW Executive Committee Elected at the 19th World Congress, Publication (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Item 6: IFBWW 19th World Congress 4-8 October 1993, the Hague, Netherlands, Publication (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Item 7: IFBWW 19th World Congress 4-8 October 1993, the Hague, Netherlands, Publication (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Item 8: IFBWW 19th Congress the Hague, Netherlands, 4-8 October 1993, Publication (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Item 9: IFBWW 19th Congress the Hague, Netherlands, 4-8 October 1993, Publication (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Item 10: IFBWW 19th Congress the Hague, Netherlands, 4-8 October 1993, Publication (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Item 11: Finding out about Women Workers: a report on IFBWWs 1992/1993 questionnaire, Publication (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Item 12: IFBWW forest programme: protecting forests - a trade union task, 1993; Publication (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Item 13: IFBWW forest programme: protecting forests - a trade union task, 1993; Publication (Box 77, Folder 11)
- Box: 77, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: 1976 New Year Message, Publication (Box 77, Folder 12)
    Author: FIET
  - Item 2: Address by H. Maier, General Secretary Fiet, to ICFTU Congress on 21 October 1975 in Mexico City, Publication (Box 77, Folder 12)
    Author: International Center of Free Trade Unionists in Exile
  - Item 3: Resolutions adopted by 22nd FIET World Congress: San Francisco, 19-23 August 1991, 1992; Publication (Box 77, Folder 12)
    Author: International Federation of Commercial, Clerical, Professional, and Technical Employees
  - Item 4: The need for a social clause in the second EEC bank directive, 1989; Publication (Box 77, Folder 12)
    Author: International Federation of Commercial, Clerical, Professional and Technical Employees
  - Item 5: Glossary of technology terms in FIET's sectors, 1983; Publication (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Item 6: Model technology agreement, 1983; Publication (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Item 7: Action programme for professional and managerial staff, 1984; Publication (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Item 8: World Action Programme: for employees in banking, insurance, commerce and industry, Publication (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Item 9: Ergonomic problems with visual display units in the banking and insurance industries, Publication (Box 77, Folder 12)
    Author: Gary K. Busch
  - Item 10: Programme for women salaried employees, 1975; Publication (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Item 11: Effects of rationalisation on the employment situation in the european commercial sector, 1975; Publication (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Item 12: Statutes of the International Federation of Commercial, Clerical, Professional and Technical Employees, Publication (Box 77, Folder 12)
- Box: 77, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Documents to further the claims of Commercial, Clerical and Technical Employees, Publication (Box 77, Folder 13)
- Box: 77, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Worldwide campaign launched to unionise managers, 1979; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
    Notes: FIET Press
  - Item 2: Rank Photocopy: International trade union council established, 1979; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: European bank und insurance employees: to beat unemployment and inflation, 1974; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: Portugal: FIET supports trade-union unity and freedom of associaiton, 1975; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 5: European Commercial workers discuss problems of unemployment, shop opening hours and fire safety measures, 1975; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 6: FIET Executive demands world policies for full employment and income security, 1975; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 7: Euro-FIET Committee takes up problems of salaried employees and Supervisory Staff, 1975; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 8: Euro-FIET Youth Committee, 1975; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 9: Euro-FIET Conference of Supervisory Staffs adopts declaration on full employment and income security, 1975; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 10: Euro-FIET bank trade section meets E.C. Commission Representatives, 1975; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 11: First General Secretary in Spain, 1975; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 12: FIET General Secretary calls on World Labour to launch new campaign for social Justice, Human dignity and Democratic values, 1975; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 13: FIET declaration on problems of Supervisory Staff, 1975; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 14: FIET General Secretary in talks with ILO Director-General, 1976; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 15: Euro-FIET Commerce Trade Section meets in Amsterdam, 1976; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 16: FIET World Executive Meets in Geneva, 1978; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 17: International Trade Union calls for arms control, 1980; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 18: FIET investigates metro-makro, 1980; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 19: ILO Director-Generneral to address FIET World Congress, 1979; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 20: Granada - Telefrent dispute may go to OECD, 1980; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 21: Rank Photocopy Council demands information disclosure, 1980; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 22: FIET Woolworth Council meets in Geneva, 1980; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 23: Bank workers and new technology, 1980; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 24: International Union campaign for trade union membership in American Bank, 1981; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 25: Rank Photocopy unions plan International protest, 1981; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 26: FIET discusses expansion of METRO/MAKRO Department Store Chain, 1981; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 27: FIET Woolworth Council seeks assurances on trade union rights from the Woolworth Parent Company, 1981; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 28: International guidelines published for work abroad, 1982; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)